strictpay.com 2010-02-07

# The Best Payment Solution - StrictPay.com

|    
February 07, 2010 3:41 pm  
---|---  
  
## Privacy Policy

StrictPay takes the privacy of your person information very seriously and will use your information only in accordance with the terms outlined in this Privacy Policy. We will not sell or rent any of your personally identifiable information to any third party. In addition, no third party will ever be able to purchase or rent a list of our customers. 

StrictPay will never reveal your bank account, or other financial information to anyone you have transferred funds to, anyone who has transferred funds to you, or any other third party. We will also notify you immediately if any person or third party requests any information concerning you or your account. 

To open an account at StrictPay you must provide your name, address, country of residence, date of birth, email address, account password, and access pin number for additional security. We may also require you to provide the answer to a security question to help verify your identity. All of the required information is necessary for us to process transactions, protect you against fraud, or in the case we need to contact you concerning your account or a transaction. If you choose not to provide the required information then you will not be able to use StrictPay's services. 

Any personally identifiable information we collect from our customers is only provided to employees who need it to help you with any customer service issues that arise, or that need to provide products or services to you. We never provide those employess with complete banking information, but they will be able to see the last four digits of any accounts you provide for identification purposes. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard any information we collect, and all financial data is stored in an encrypted format. Any time we transfer information over the internet we use an encryption system utilizing a 256-bit SSL certificate. 

By checking the boxes concerning Terms of Service and Privacy Policy during the signup process, you are agreeing to our use of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or anything else concerning StrictPay, please contact our support center here.   
  
---  
  
Copyright © 2010 StrictPay.com - All Rights Reserved
